<data>
	<pageText id="tab0">
		<![CDATA[Module Overview]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="tab1">
		<![CDATA[Learning Outcomes]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="tab2">
		<![CDATA[Assignments]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_1">
		<![CDATA[As you probably learned in a high school civics class, in the <abbr title="United States">U.S.</abbr> system of government lawmakers create laws, executives enforce them, and courts rule on them; however, the actual process of administering laws is more complicated than this. For instance, if a state government creates a law for obtaining drivers licenses, the lawmakers themselves cannot accept, review, and decide every individual application for that license. Similarly, lawmakers cannot individually determine if a single workplace safety violation is worthy of a fine or whether or not a specific manufacturer is meeting particular environmental regulations. Instead, governments create administrative agencies to accomplish these and many other important tasks.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_2">
		<![CDATA[In this module, you will learn how and why administrative agencies are created, the kinds of agencies that are created, and the relationship between these agencies and the other components of government at the federal, state, and local levels. You will also learn how administrative agencies are controlled and regulated through the Administrative Procedure Act (<abbr title="Administrative Procedure Act">APA</abbr>), and about the important differences between federal statutes and agency rules and regulations. We will finish the module with a discussion of an administrative agency in the news and a weekly assignment that asks you to investigate the relationship between a hypothetical employer and <abbr title="Occupational Safety and Health Administration">OSHA</abbr>’s laws and regulations.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_3">
		<![CDATA[The readings and assignments for this module are based on the following learning outcomes:]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_4">
		<![CDATA[Differentiate between legislation/statutes and agency regulations/rules.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_5">
		<![CDATA[Describe how agency rules and regulations are promulgated and the limits on administrative agency authority.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_6">
		<![CDATA[Identify the various federal, state, and local agencies regulating the student’s field of work.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_7">
		<![CDATA[Examine how administrative agencies enforce and adjudicate law and policy.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_8">
		<![CDATA[The assignments in this module will require you to research administrative agencies and share your experiences or encounters with administrative agencies.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_9">
		<![CDATA[In the discussion, you will demonstrate your understanding about the different types of administrative agencies and the kinds of powers exercised by them. In the written assignment, you will create a report for an administrative agency based on a scenario.]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_10">
		<![CDATA[You will complete two major assignments known as <abbr title="Learning Assessment System Assignments">LASA</abbr>s in this course. These assignments are due in <strong>Modules 3</strong> and <strong>5</strong>.]]>
	</pageText>
</data>