<data>
	<pageDesc>
		<![CDATA[This is the summary page of the module. Containing image top and text bottom.]]>
	</pageDesc>
	<pageText id="txt_title-01">
		<![CDATA[Summary Page Heading]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_1">
		<![CDATA[In this module, you have learned the following:]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="txt_2">
		<![CDATA[<ul>		<li>Administrative agencies play a critical role in the <abbr title="United States">U.S.<abbr> legal system. After Congress passes a law, someone has to implement it. The main role of federal administrative agencies is to implement laws passed by Congress.<li>		<li>The laws passed by Congress are known as <em>statutes<em>. Often, the statutes set broad standards but do not specify how those standards should be interpreted. In order to add further detail and interpretation to the laws passed by Congress, agencies often enact rules and regulations. The statute that the agency is charged with implementing is known by a number of names, including the “enabling act,” “enabling statute,” “organic act,” and “organic statute.” <li>		<li>When agencies create rules, they are said to engage in the regulatory process. The agency must follow certain processes and procedures, including the Administrative Procedure Act, along with the agency’s enabling statute.<li>		<li>In addition to rulemaking, the second main area of agency activity is known as adjudication, or the process of deciding how the agency’s enabling act should apply in specific situations to specific parties. Like rulemaking, the agency must follow the right procedures required by the <abbr title="Administrative Procedure Act">APA<abbr> and the agency’s own statute.<li>		<li>Many state and local agencies exist, although the course will generally focus on federal agencies. Often, a single business or person can be regulated by many different agencies at the federal, state, and local level.<li>		<ul>]]>
	</pageText>
	<pageText id="sprite4">
		<![CDATA[<p>asdf asdfasf asf</p>]]>
	</pageText>
</data>